They're back in the saddle!
City Slickers II: The Legend of Curly's Gold is a comedy,
western film directed by Paul Weiland.
Mitch Robbins' 40th birthday begins quite well until he returns home and finds
his brother Glen, the black sheep of the family, in his sofa.
Nevertheless he is about to have a wonderful birthday-night with his
wife when he discovers a treasure map of Curly by chance.
Together with Phil and unfortunately Glen he tries to find the
hidden gold of Curly's father in the desert of Arizona.
Mitch Robbins, played by Billy Crystal.
Phil Berquist, played by Daniel Stern.
Glen Robbins, played by Jon Lovitz.
Duke Page, played by Jack Palance.
Barbara Robbins, played by Patricia Wettig.
Bud, played by Pruitt Taylor Vince.
City Slickers II: The Legend of Curly's Gold is a 1994 American
Western comedy film directed by Paul Weiland.
It is the sequel to City Slickers (1991) and stars Billy
Crystal, Daniel Stern, Jon Lovitz and Jack Palance.
The film was released on June 10, 1994 by Columbia Pictures.
Although it was a mild financial success grossing $72 million against a $40 million budget, the film did
not reach the popularity of the first, receiving generally negative responses from critics.
The film explores themes of gold, birthday, nevada,
treasure hunt, friendship bracelet.
The tone is lighthearted.